chubbyparade.com 2009-06-17

# Chubby Parade Privacy Policy

Your privacy is of the utmost importance to us. Because we ask for some basic personal information during registration, we want you to be fully informed of how this information is gathered and used.

1\. REGISTRATION  
2\. INFORMATION CHUBBYPARADE REQUESTS  
3\. CHILDREN'S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT  
4\. PARTICIPATION  
5\. EMAIL MESSAGES  
9\. PUBLIC FORUMS  
10\. SECURITY  
11\. TERMINATION  
12\. SUMMARY

**Registration**  
Some basic personal information is required in order to register with the Chubby Parade:

* Date of birth - If you are under 18 years (or under legal age of your region), you are not allowed to use the Chubbyparade forums.  
* Email Address - By providing your email address, you can receive important messages via your existing email account. Message board notifications (thread subscriptions) and messages sent to you by other ChubbyParade forum users rely on the email address you provide when you register.  
You need to supply a valid email address in order to activate your account.  
* User Name - This is how you are identified when you participate in forums. While many other aspects of your account can be updated regularly, your user name cannot be changed.

**Information Chubbyparade Requests**  
When you register, you are asked to give basic demographic information (like birth year and gender). We ask you to tell us a little about yourself so we can better understand the types of people who register. 

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**  
No children under 18 are allowed to participate in the Chubby Parade Forums.

The forum's pages are labelled with [ICRA](http://www.icra.org/) and [restricted to adults](http://restrictedtoadults.org/).

**Participation**  
The above describes information that is provided "actively" - meaning, you choose to submit this information to us when you join the Chubbyparade forum, or update your account at any point after having joined. Some other information is provided "passively" - meaning, that Chubbyparade obtains this information when you login to your account and use the service. This is done primarily through the use of "cookies." Cookies are used on the Chubbyparade to verify your login information, and to optionally store your password in your browser so that you do not need to type it in each time you visit. Any time that you point your browser to a 'members-only' area, Chubbyparade checks your browser's cookie file to see if you have already logged in, and if you have, you're taken right to the page that you have requested. If not, you'll be directed to the Chubbyparade login screen, where you can quickly and easily login to your account, or signup for the Chubbyparade forum if you are not yet a member.

**Email Messages**  
As a registered user, you may receive informational email messages from the Chubbyparade forum. These messages are only sent on extraordinary occasions (for example site downtimes, opening of new forums for specific user groups).

Thread subscriptions can be turned off during registration or in the [User Control Panel](http://chubbyparade.com/forum/usercp.php).  
During signup or in the Control Panel, you can choose to not receive email notifications on new private messages.

We will never disclose your personal information (like for example your email address) to anybody.

**Public Forums**  
Chubbyparade is a public message board. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in the forums and the chat becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  
In no case should you publish your personal contact information (like your telephone number, email address or your postal address).

**Security**  
Chubbyparade.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information of its users. The Chubbyparade's server has strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about its users.

**Termination**  
You can elect to terminate your membership at the Chubbyparade at any time.  
If you want your user account deleted, please contact [Admin](http://chubbyparade.com/forum/private.php?do=newpm&u=1).

**Summary**  
In this electronic era, when personal information can easily be obtained through various sources, we appreciate the sensitivity of any private information that you disclose to us. It is our intention to treat your account information with the highest level of care.  
Your personal information will _not_ be disclosed to third parties.
